shoestring.com.au 2013-05-09

# WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY

WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY
     DATED: 12th November 2012

Website Privacy Policy
                          WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY
This web site is owned and operated by Shoe String Media Group Pty Ltd and will be
referred to as "We", "our" and "us" in this Internet Privacy Policy. By using this site, you
agree to the Internet Privacy Policy of this web site ("the web site"), which is set out on this
web site page. The Internet Privacy Policy relates to the collection and use of personal
information you may supply to us through your conduct on the web site.
We reserve the right, at our discretion, to modify or remove portions of this Internet Privacy
Policy at any time. This Internet Privacy Policy is in addition to any other terms and
conditions applicable to the web site. We do not make any representations about third party
web sites that may be linked to the web site.
We recognise the importance of protecting the privacy of information collected about visitors
to our web site, in particular information that is capable of identifying an individual
("personal information"). This Internet Privacy Policy governs the manner in which your
personal information, obtained through the web site, will be dealt with. This Internet Privacy
Policy should be reviewed periodically so that you are updated on any changes. We welcome
your comments and feedback.
Personal Information
1.    Personal information about visitors to our site is collected only when knowingly and
      voluntarily submitted. For example, we may need to collect such information to provide
      you with further services or to answer or forward any requests or enquiries. It is our
      intention that this policy will protect your personal information from being dealt with in
      any way that is inconsistent with applicable privacy laws in Australia.
Use of Information
2.    Personal information that visitors submit to our site is used only for the purpose for
      which it is submitted or for such other secondary purposes that are related to the
      primary purpose, unless we disclose other uses in this Internet Privacy Policy or at the
      time of collection. Copies of correspondence sent from the web site, that may contain
      personal information, are stored as archives for record-keeping and back-up purposes
      only.
Collecting information on Registered members
3.    As part of registering with us, we collect personal information about you in order for
      you to take full advantage of our services. To do this it may be necessary for you to
      provide additional information to us as detailed below.
4.    Registration
      Registration is completely optional. Registration may include submitting your name,
                                                                                      Page 1 of 3

Website Privacy Policy
      email address, address, telephone numbers, option on receiving updates and
      promotional material and other information. You may access this information at any
      time by logging in and going to your account.
Credit Card Details
5.    Credit Card details are only stored for the processing of payment and will be deleted
      once payment is processed.
Disclosure
6.    Apart from where you have consented or disclosure is necessary to achieve the purpose
      for which it was submitted, personal information may be disclosed in special situations
      where we have reason to believe that doing so is necessary to identify, contact or bring
      legal action against anyone damaging, injuring, or interfering (intentionally or
      unintentionally) with our rights or property, users, or anyone else who could be harmed
      by such activities. Also, we may disclose personal information when we believe in
      good faith that the law requires disclosure.
7.    We may engage third parties to provide you with goods or services on our behalf. In
      that circumstance, we may disclose your personal information to those third parties in
      order to meet your request for goods or services.
Security
8.    We strive to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of personal information
      submitted to our sites, and we review and update our security measures in light of
      current technologies. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be
      guaranteed to be totally secure.
9.    However, we will endeavour to take all reasonable steps to protect the personal
      information you may transmit to us or from our online products and services. Once we
      do receive your transmission, we will also make our best efforts to ensure its security
      on our systems.
10.   In addition, our employees and the contractors who provide services related to our
      information systems are obliged to respect the confidentiality of any personal
      information held by us. However, we will not be held responsible for events arising
      from unauthorised access to your personal information.
Collecting Information from Users
11.   IP Addresses
      Our web servers gather your IP address to assist with the diagnosis of problems or
      support issues with our services. Again, information is gathered in aggregate only and
                                                                                     Page 2 of 3

Website Privacy Policy
      cannot be traced to an individual user.
12.   Cookies and Applets
      We use cookies to provide you with a better experience. These cookies allow us to
      increase your security by storing your session ID and are a way of monitoring single
      user access.
      This aggregate, non-personal information is collated and provided to us to assist in
      analysing the usage of the site.
Access to Information
13.   We will endeavour to take all reasonable steps to keep secure any information which
      we hold about you, and to keep this information accurate and up to date. If, at any time,
      you discover that information held about you is incorrect, you may contact us to have
      the information corrected.
14.   In addition, our employees and the contractors who provide services related to our
      information systems are obliged to respect the confidentiality of any personal
      information held by us.
Links to other sites
15.   We provide links to Web sites outside of our web sites, as well as to third party Web
      sites. These linked sites are not under our control, and we cannot accept responsibility
      for the conduct of companies linked to our website. Before disclosing your personal
      information on any other website, we advise you to examine the terms and conditions
      of using that Web site and its privacy statement.
Problems or questions
16.   If we become aware of any ongoing concerns or problems with our web sites, we will
      take these issues seriously and work to address these concerns. If you have any further
      queries relating to our Privacy Policy, or you have a problem or complaint, please
      contact us.
17.   For more information about privacy issues in Australia and protecting your privacy,
      visit     the    Australian      Federal    Privacy     Commissioner's      web       site;
      http://www.privacy.gov.au/.
This Privacy Policy has been specifically drafted for and provided to Shoe String Media
Group Pty Ltd by LawLive Pty Ltd (www.lawlive.com.au).
                                                                                      Page 3 of 3
